Guide to the World War II servicemen alumni files, class years 1939-1945.
World War II servicemen alumni files
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
World War II servicemen alumni files, class years 1939-1945.
41-2-822
3 cubic feet
Correspondence, newspapers, photographs
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, photographs, clippings, and biographical data concerning Cornell University alumni who died during World War II.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, photographs, clippings, and biographical data concerning Cornell University alumni who died during World War II.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.
Subjects:
World War, 1939-1945.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
For all other alumni, see Cornell deceased alumni files, #41-2-877.
CONTAINER LIST
- World War II. Memorial Record (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Ackerknecht, PFC. William Charles 1945 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Adams, Lt. Robert Copeland 1942 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Alpern, ETM Daniel 1946 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Anderson, Bror Henry 1937 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Anderson, Lt. Lewis Alfred 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Andrews, William John 1943 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Andrulis, Anthony John 1943 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Andrus, Walton Roosevelt 1945 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Arthur Jr., 2nd Lt. William Churchill 1946 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Ashman, Robert Irving 1940 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Ashton, Henry 1935 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Auld, 1st Sgt. Robert Graham 1946 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Austen, Lt. Robert Lewis 1946 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Ayrault III, Lt. (JG) George (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Babitsky, Charles 1939 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Bakewell, Chief Warrant Officer Joseph Hunter 1903 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Baldwin, Louis Lester 1942 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Ballway, 1st LT. Harold Edward 1937 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Bamberger, Joseph James 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Banfield, Hugh William Ward 1939 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Barker, Sgt. Edwin Bogue Jr. 1934 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Barnes, Lt. Col. Louis Dwight 1911 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Barnum, Capt. Eugene Everett, Jr. 1941 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Barnum, William James 1938 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Barth, Gen. Charles Henry, Jr. 1927 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Bassett, Capt. Dell Claire 1925 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Bassett, Lt. Norman Banks 1945 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Baumann, Lt. John Roland Jr. 1938 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Baxter, Eric 1921 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Bedell, Harry Nathaniel Jr. 1942 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Bemis, William Joseph, Jr. 1927 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Benjamin, Lt. Earl Whitney 1943 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Bennett, Clifford E. Spec. (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Berkowitz, Paul Henry Grad. (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Bertull, Henry Med. (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Bilon, Lawrence Joseph 1940 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Blanchard, 1st. Lt. James Loren 1943 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Bleich, F/O Herbert J. 1944 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Blue, Lt. Malcolm Leonard 1943 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Bostwick, Major James Montgomery 1940 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Bowen Jr., Lt. Charles Tracy 1943 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Bowman, Robert Clinton (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Briggs, Ensign Mead Lynn 1945 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Brokenshire, Lt. Comdr. Herbert Cecil Grad. (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Brownback, Joseph Mueller 1937 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Broten, John Oscar 1942 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Bougham, PFC. Robert Earl 1943 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Brower, Gerald Evans 1916 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Brown, Capt. Alvin Chauncey 1920 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Brown, Carey Herbert Jr. 1941 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Brown, Fenton Elmer 1943 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Brown, Ens. Sylvester O. 1946 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Brunson, Robert Taft 1941 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Private Gerhard Buehler (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Bullard, 1st Lt. Jonathan Harrington 1942 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Bullard, Richard Division 1927 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Bundy, Leon Horace 1932 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Burlew, Pvt. Harry Elwyn 1942 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Burnett, PM 3/c William Robert 1946 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Burns, William Sherman, Jr. 1943 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Calderaci, Cpl. Donald Kenneth Townsend 1946 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Cameron, Donald Grad. (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Campbell, William Todd 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Carey, Lt. (jg) William Robert 1945 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Carmen, Elliott 1942 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Carpenter, 1st Lt. John Dwight 1943 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Carpenter, Margaret Hallowell 1935 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Carter, 1st Lt. John Leavitt 1943 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Cascio, Dominick Donald 1930 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Catlin, George Dorrance 1942 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Chrystall, 1st Lt. David 1938 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Church, Jr., 1st Lt. Lloyd 1939 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Clark, Lt. George Joseph 1941 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Clark, John Spencer Sp Agr (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Clark, Ronald, Jr. 1946 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Clements, James William 1942 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Collins, 1st Lt. Richard Kenneth 1940 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Comerford, John Philip 1945 (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Conroe, PFC. Edward G. 1946 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Cook, Pvt. Robert Eugene 1946 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Cooper, Corp. Seth Robin 1941 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Corbisello, Joseph John 1946 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Coyne, Lt. j.g. John Harding 1942 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Cox, Col. Joseph Winston, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Capt. Orrin F. Crankshaw Med. (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Crebbs, Ens. Ben Herbert 1943 (Box 1, Folder 87)
- 1st Lt. Crofoot David Wilson 1923 (Box 1, Folder 88)
- Crowe, Peter Emmet 1942 (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Cullinan, Paul William 1942 (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Cuthbert, Lowell Douglas 1940 (Box 1, Folder 91)
- Dalberth, Arthur Charles 1941 (Box 1, Folder 92)
- Dallenbach, Lt. John Wallace Grad. (Box 1, Folder 93)
- Dalton, Lt. Philip 1924 (Box 1, Folder 94)
- Darrow, Norman 1940 (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Datthyn, Lester J. 1942 (Box 1, Folder 96)
- Davenport, John Blackwell Jr. Grad. (Box 1, Folder 97)
- Davidson, Alexander Parkhill, Jr. 1942 (Box 1, Folder 98)
- Davis, Clay Robinson 1939 (Box 1, Folder 99)
- Davis, 2nd Lt. Ralph Theodore 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 100)
- Dayton, Lt. James Henry 1942 (Box 1, Folder 101)
- Deabler, Richard Thurston 1941 (Box 1, Folder 102)
- De Golyer, Lt. Willard Thurman 1940 (Box 1, Folder 103)
- De Grasse, 1st Lt. Victor Richard 1935 (Box 1, Folder 104)
- Dellapenta, Pvt. William Joseph 1945 (Box 1, Folder 105)
- Detwyler, Richard Elroy 1941 (Box 1, Folder 106)
- Dodd, John Gray 1942 (Box 1, Folder 107)
- Dohner, A/C Harold Bertram 1944 (Box 1, Folder 108)
- Dolezal, PFC. John Robert 1944 (Box 1, Folder 109)
- Doubrava, Herbert John 1943 (Box 1, Folder 110)
- Downs, Charles A. 1945 (Box 1, Folder 111)
- Dudley, James Roe 1941 (Box 1, Folder 112)
- Duignan, V Pvt. James Guernsey 1943 (Box 1, Folder 113)
- Durbin, Capt. Richard Mott 1941 (Box 1, Folder 114)
- Durland, Russell Wickham 1941 (Box 1, Folder 115)
- Dusenberry, Charles Edward, Jr. 1938-1940 (Box 1, Folder 116)
- Edsall, 2nd Lt. Richard Perry 1943 (Box 1, Folder 117)
- 2nd Lt. Howard W. Eggert SP. AGR (Box 1, Folder 118)
- Eisenman, William Hunt (JR.) 1943 (Box 1, Folder 119)
- Ekeberg, John Clayton AVS 1941 (Box 1, Folder 120)
- Ellis, Lt. Edward Porter USNR 1936 (Box 1, Folder 121)
- Eldred, Capt. Warren Brooks 1912 (Box 1, Folder 122)
- Ely, Richard MC Brier 1938 (Box 1, Folder 123)
- Ely, Theodore Benjamin, Jr. 1942 (Box 1, Folder 124)
- Engel, PFC Robert Hans 1945 (Box 1, Folder 125)
- Engles, Flight Officer Richard Jerome 1945 (Box 1, Folder 126)
- Estey, PFC. Jacob 1946 (Box 1, Folder 127)
- Eubank, James Norvell, Jr. 1938 (Box 1, Folder 128)
- Evans, 1st Lt. Robert Jay 1943 (Box 1, Folder 129)
- Farber, Benjamin Franklin Jr. 1937 (Box 1, Folder 130)
- Farley, Thomas Joyce USNR 1947 (Box 1, Folder 131)
- Feight, Howard Washington 1927 (Box 1, Folder 132)
- Feinson, Lt. Col. Samuel Henry 1922 (Box 1, Folder 133)
- Fitzpatrick, Lt. Frank James 1943 (Box 1, Folder 134)
- Fleischer, Aaron Benjamin A.V.S. 1944 (Box 1, Folder 135)
- Flessa, Donald Karl Med. (Box 1, Folder 136)
- Flohr, Jerome 1938 (Box 1, Folder 137)
- Forbush, Lt. Wallace Clifford 1942 (Box 1, Folder 138)
- Forrest Jr., 2nd Lt. Lawrence Raymond 1944 (Box 1, Folder 139)
- Frank, Stanley 1934 (Box 1, Folder 140)
- Frazer, Capt. Trumbull Med. (Box 1, Folder 141)
- Fricke, William Hobson, AUS 1946 (Box 1, Folder 142)
- Fries, 1st Lt. William Robert 1935 (Box 1, Folder 143)
- Frost Jr., Lt. Robert Theodore 1943 (Box 1, Folder 144)
- Furman, David 1938 (Box 1, Folder 145)
- Galloway, Theodore Frederick 1942 (Box 1, Folder 146)
- Gang, Lt. Comdr. Victor MC-USNR 1933 (Box 1, Folder 147)
- Gard, Clifford Rohr 1919 (Box 1, Folder 148)
- Gavaris, William Theodore 1943 (Box 1, Folder 149)
- Gavett, Robert Malcolm Comdr. 1918 (Box 1, Folder 150)
- Gavitt, CPL. Richard Lester 1946 (Box 1, Folder 151)
- Geddes, Joseph Woolley Grad. (Box 1, Folder 152)
- George, Charles Oswin 1940 (Box 1, Folder 153)
- Gerst, Robert Francis Grad. (Box 1, Folder 154)
- Gerstley, Greil Isaac 1941 (Box 1, Folder 155)
- Gilbert, Jr., 1st Lt. William T. 1946 (Box 1, Folder 156)
- Gillies, Pvt. William John 1945 (Box 1, Folder 157)
- Golluber, Gerald 1932 (Box 1, Folder 158)
- Good, Capt. Herbert F. 1921 (Box 1, Folder 159)
- Goodman, Flight Officer Jerome David 1944 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Gordon, Sgt. Henry G. 1945 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Gordon, Jacob Stephen 1944 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Gordon, William Mortimer Grad. 1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Gorman, Clarence John 1921 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Goulko, Burton Thorwald 1942 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Gove, Richard Capt. Everest 1920 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Graham, John Winston 1941 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Gray, 1st Lt. Lawrence Barr 1940 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Greenbaum, Eugene 1947 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Grimshaw, Frederick George, Jr. 1942 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Guggenheimer, John 1937 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Gurman, David Allen 1943 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Hambleton, Roscoe Lee 1917 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Hamilton, Charles Frazine Jr. 1928 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Hanley, 2nd Lt. Edward Joseph 1942 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Hanshaw, John George 1931 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Harmon, David 1931 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Harwood, Jonathan Hartweell, Jr. 1942 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Hays, Jr., 1st Lt. Ralph Langdon 1943 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Healy, Lt. George Eugene 1940 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Heath, Ellis George 1942 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Heimes, Sgt. Fred John 1940 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Helps, PFC. Ronald William 1946 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Henderson, Bruce G. 1945 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Hene, Julius Anhalt 1928 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Henrich, John William, Jr. 1928 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Hermance, 1st Lt. Alan Edgar 1939 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Hermann, Burton Covert 1940 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Hershey, Lt. Lester 1946 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Hewitt, George Frederick 3d 1943 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Hickey, Gerald Frederick 1935 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Hicks, P.F.C. William Preston 1933 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Hills, James Seymour 1946 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Hintgen, Lt. (j.g.) Gene Louis 1939 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Hobson, Ens. John Davidson 1946 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Holland, 1st Lt. Glen A. 1943 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Horlick, Ens. John Haynes 1945 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Horn, Stanley James 1928 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Hornung, A/C John Andrew 1946 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Horwitz, David 1936 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Horowitz, William Harold A.V.S. 1944 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Hough, Romeyn Beck, Jr. 1919 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Howard, 2nd Lt. Charles Henry 1944 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Howe, Lt. Robert Louis 1935 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Howes, 2nd Lt. James Thomas 1939 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Hoyt, John Davidson Hill 1920 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Huey, Ralph Leonard 1941 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Huffcut, Lt. Robert James 1938 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Hungerford, Stanley Willcox 1945 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Hunt, Arthur Clarendon 1929 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Huntington III, Ellery Channing1946 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Ideler, Martin AUS 1946 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Ingham, Lt. Thomas Sheppard, Jr. 1943 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Ingles, John Thomas 1943 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Irving, Charles Edward 1942 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Isham, S/sgt. Robert Haynes 1945 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Jackson, John West 1942 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Jacobius, Capt. Herman L. Med. (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Jansen, Richard Stuart 1943 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Johnson, Raymond Edward 1942 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Johnson, Lt. Thomas Wells Grad. (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Johnson Walter Robert Med. (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Jones, Lt. Arthur Duane USNR 1935 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Josefson, Hyman 1929 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Joseph, William Paul 1942 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Josephson, Melvin Donald 1946 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Kearns, 2nd Lt. Charles MI Chael, Jr. AUS 1942 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Kelly, 1st Lt. Edward Thomas 1941 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Keltch, Ens. Rubin 1941 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Kern, Lt. George Henry 1931 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Kernochan, 2nd Lt. John Benson 1942 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Ketcham, Ens. John Stanley 1945 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- King, John Robinson 1940 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Kiple, Lt. Peter Edwin 1939 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Kiyak, John Joseph 1941 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Kleinhofer, Carl Joseph 1944 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Knight, James Percy 1937 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Knight, Richard Smith AUS. 1942 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Knoerl, George Anthony 1942 (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Knott, Dickson Randolph 1942 (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Krell, A/S Clyde Herbert 1948 (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Koch, Jr., Lt. Louis J.AUS 1944 (Box 2, Folder 83)
- Koch, 2nd Lt. William Conrad 1946 (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Koshkin, Lt. Eugene 1940 (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Koslan, Sgt. Alfred Samuel 1942 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Kruvant, Lt. Arnold Berton 1940 (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Kuppinger, 1st Lt. Harold Richard 1938 (Box 2, Folder 88)
- Kyte, Lt. Floyd Douglas 1941 (Box 2, Folder 89)
- Labombarde, S 2/C William Hobart 1948 (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Landsberg, Lt. John Joseph 1945 (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Langhammer, William Paul 1938 (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Larlee, Howard Boyce 1937 (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Laslocky, Emory Ernest 1946 (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Laubenstein, William Julius 1927 (Box 2, Folder 95)
- Lednum, Ens. Maynard Friz 1945 (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Levin, 1st Lt. Arthur Landis 1938 (Box 2, Folder 97)
- Lindheim, Donald Robert AUS. 1935 (Box 2, Folder 98)
- Link, Albert Edmund 1930 (Box 2, Folder 99)
- Loewenberg, Capt. Stanley Arthur 1931 (Box 2, Folder 100)
- Logan, Stanley Harold Grad. (Box 2, Folder 101)
- Lothrop, Major Robert Blake 1933 (Box 2, Folder 102)
- Lukcso, Pfc. William Ernest 1946 (Box 2, Folder 103)
- Ludwig, 1st Lt. Edward Earl, Jr. 1943 (Box 2, Folder 104)
- Lull, Raymond Albert 1938 (Box 2, Folder 105)
- Mackaye, Cpl. James Steward 1941 (Box 2, Folder 106)
- Madden, Robert Warner 1945 (Box 2, Folder 107)
- Maggs, Donald Frederick 1943 (Box 2, Folder 108)
- Malley, Lt. Francis Xavier, Jr. 1946 (Box 2, Folder 109)
- Marchant, Richard Wescom 1938 (Box 2, Folder 110)
- Marks, Herbert Joseph 1942 (Box 2, Folder 111)
- Marshland, James Lyster 1941 (Box 2, Folder 112)
- Martindale, Lt. John Homer 1940 (Box 2, Folder 113)
- Mason, 1st Lt. John Mansfield 1943 (Box 2, Folder 114)
- Mathews, F-O William Hooker, Jr. 1940 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- McCarthy, Parnell James AUS. Grad. (Box 2, Folder 116)
- McKendrick, Charles Vance 1941 (Box 2, Folder 117)
- Ma Kirdy, Col. Howard Spencer Med. (Box 2, Folder 118)
- McLaughlin Jr., Capt. John A. 1933 (Box 2, Folder 119)
- McMullin, S/Sgt. John Beverly 1945 (Box 2, Folder 120)
- McNeill, 1st Lt. Herbert Warren 1941 (Box 2, Folder 121)
- Mears Lyman Forbes 1927 (Box 2, Folder 122)
- Meltzer, Seymour B. 1941 (Box 2, Folder 123)
- Merton, John Paul 1939 (Box 2, Folder 124)
- Meyer, 1st Lt. Emil Francis Meyer 1935 (Box 2, Folder 125)
- Millar, 1st Lt. Harold Hutcheon 1944 (Box 2, Folder 126)
- Miller, James Tripp 1940 (Box 2, Folder 127)
- Milliman, Ens. Leonard Treman 1940 (Box 2, Folder 128)
- Mitchell, Capt. Anthony B. 1942 (Box 2, Folder 129)
- Mitchell, Lt. John Lendrum 1942 (Box 2, Folder 130)
- Moffat, Colonel Reuben Curtis 1918 (Box 2, Folder 131)
- Monsees, Sgt. George 1941 (Box 2, Folder 132)
- Moon, Donald Herbert 1940 (Box 2, Folder 133)
- Moravec, Pfc. Stanley Philip Spec. (Box 2, Folder 134)
- Morgan, Sgt. George Alexander Sp. Agr. (Box 2, Folder 135)
- Morgan, Lt. George Jasper 1936 (Box 2, Folder 136)
- Morrill, Charles William, Jr. 1944 (Box 2, Folder 137)
- Morris, Lt. Edgar Dunbar Jr. 1945 (Box 2, Folder 138)
- Morris, Fred Harold 1941 (Box 2, Folder 139)
- Mowson, William Frederick 1946 (Box 2, Folder 140)
- Pvt. Edward D. Mueden 1947 (Box 2, Folder 141)
- 2nd Lt. William Dier Mulberry 1941 (Box 2, Folder 142)
- Mulner, Lt. Martin Hamilton 1945 (Box 2, Folder 143)
- Nardi, Lt. (jg) John Louis 1942 (Box 2, Folder 144)
- Natapow, Donald Leon 1943 (Box 2, Folder 145)
- Neal, S/Sgt. James William 1939 (Box 2, Folder 146)
- Neumann, John 1947 (Box 2, Folder 147)
- Newbold, Lt. William C. 1945 (Box 2, Folder 148)
- Noble, Jay Alvin, Jr. 1938 (Box 2, Folder 149)
- Noble, 2nd Lt. William Frederick 1938 (Box 2, Folder 150)
- O'Connell, Lt. (j.g.) William Stephen, Jr. 1939 (Box 2, Folder 151)
- Ogi, Verner Frederick 1937 (Box 2, Folder 152)
- O'Hara, Lt. Harry John 1945 (Box 2, Folder 153)
- Oliver, Clifford Rylander, Jr. 1937 (Box 2, Folder 154)
- Olney, James Philip 1946 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Olson, Fred Sherman 1942 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- O'Neal, Richard Carroll 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Oonk, Donald Alfred 1944 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Orange, Herbert Edward 1928 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Osberg, Carl August 1942 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Page, Edward Forrest Jr. 1945 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Palmer, William Frederick 1940 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Parkhill, Donald Barnes 1942 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Parkhurt, Roger Williams 1913 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Pascual, Raymond (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Pate, Robert Dale 1946 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Pearson, John Augustus 1941 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Pelton, Richard Millington 1937 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Pendleton, Fields S. 1946 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Pellman, Seymour Edward 1946 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Percy, Joseph Henry 1934 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Percy, William Robert 1941 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Perrin, Edward Joseph 1940 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Peterson, Cyrus Lawrence (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Pfeffer, Walter F. 1944 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Phelps, Alfred Earl 1942 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Pickell, Hugh Alton (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Pirie, James M. (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Plaine, Irving 1934 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Polensky, Monroe Jesse Grad (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Polin, Marvin Henry 1941 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Poole, Frank Bernard 1937 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Powell, Raleigh Cox Jr. Grad (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Powell, Richard Chew Jr. 1940 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Powers, Robert Neil 1943 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Puterbaugh, John Louis 1935 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Ramsdell, Raymond Chester 1945 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Ransom, Richard Laffler 1943 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Rathgeb, Irving Roy 1934 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Raymer, Clifford Benjamin 1933 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Reddert, William Parker 1947 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Reddout, Clayton Champ 1940 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Reed, Kenneth Owen 1941 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Reed, Ralph Eugene 1946 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Reeks, Charles Pavalar 1942 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Rees, William David 1945 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Reeves, Robert John 1940 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Reimers, Frederick Fay 1939 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Reinstatler, Cyril Joseph 1944 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Retan, George Owen 1945 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Rhodes, Carl Fearnley 1938 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Richardson, Malcolm Trone 1945 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Richey, David H. 1946 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Robb, John Larkin 1945 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Robbins, Warren David 1923 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Rockmore, Claytons 1943 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Ross, Harold Lacey Jr. 1944 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Rothra, Virgil Harold 1933 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Rooney, John Daley 1939 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Rosenblum, Haskell Benjamin 1933 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Rosenfeld, George R. 1944 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Rubin, Malcolm Hirsch 1944 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Rumsey, Williston Fish Grad (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Safro, Victor Israel 1909 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Sailor, Laurence Seaton 1927 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Sandler, Joseph 1927 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Saphier, Jacques Conrad 1936 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Saville, Irwin George 1945 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Sayer, Albert Horton 1937 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Schlener, John Lucius Jr. 1941 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Schoedel, Adrian Collison 1930 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Schrader, Robert Kenneth Grad (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Schultz, Thomas Arthur 1940 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Schurmann, Ralph Louis 1946 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Schweitzer, George Frank 1943 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Scott, Robert Ross 1941 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Seiffert, Robert Fulton III 1935 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Seitz, Henry William (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Sells, William Dunningham 1936 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Sherwood, Kenneth Sylverster 1944 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- Sherwood, Nial Jr. 1941 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Sivade, Francis Elie 1940 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- Slavin, Robert Israel 1945 (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Shavely, Carl Grey Jr. 1942 (Box 3, Folder 81)
- Shitow, Stanley Joel 1940 (Box 3, Folder 82)
- Sophian, Abraham Jr. 1941 (Box 3, Folder 83)
- Sowden, Thomas Chandler 1934 (Box 3, Folder 84)
- Spear, James Dreyfus 1941 (Box 3, Folder 85)
- Spicer, Emmet Robinson Med (Box 3, Folder 86)
- Spicer, Raymond Gilbert 1942 (Box 3, Folder 87)
- Stanton, Clifford Alfred Jr. 1942 (Box 3, Folder 88)
- Stenstrom, Fred Henry 1939 (Box 3, Folder 89)
- Stephens, Walker C. 1944 (Box 3, Folder 90)
- Stern, Arnold 1943 (Box 3, Folder 91)
- Stevenson, Robert L. 1945 (Box 3, Folder 92)
- Stewart, Charles West Jr. 1926 (Box 3, Folder 93)
- Stewart, Ralph Wentworth 1932 (Box 3, Folder 94)
- Stillwell, Herbert Edward 1945 (Box 3, Folder 95)
- Stillwell, Winslow William 1942 (Box 3, Folder 96)
- Storie, Robert Kennedy 1935 (Box 3, Folder 97)
- Stricker, Harold Louis Jr. 1935 (Box 3, Folder 98)
- Strobel, William Howard 1935 (Box 3, Folder 99)
- Sunshine, Alvin Bruce, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 100)
- Sussman, Donald Frank 1941 (Box 3, Folder 101)
- Swan, Daniel Nanny Jr. 1910 (Box 3, Folder 102)
- Swenson, John William 1928 (Box 3, Folder 103)
- Taliaferro, Albert Pendleton Jr. 1922 (Box 3, Folder 104)
- Taylor, Robert Dudley 1945 (Box 3, Folder 105)
- Teegarden, John Maxon 1941 (Box 3, Folder 106)
- Terrill, Winton Frederick 1939 (Box 3, Folder 107)
- Thompson, Henry Lawrence 1940 (Box 3, Folder 108)
- Thackston, Richard King Grad (Box 3, Folder 109)
- Thomas, John B. 1943 (Box 3, Folder 110)
- Thompson, Arnold William 1940 (Box 3, Folder 111)
- Thompson, Arthur Lee III 1943 (Box 3, Folder 112)
- Timerman, Claude D. 1941 (Box 3, Folder 113)
- Timmerman, Henry Lincoln 1946 (Box 3, Folder 114)
- Tinley, Charles David Grad (Box 3, Folder 115)
- Todd, Norman Mackintosh 1944 (Box 3, Folder 116)
- Toffey, John James Jr. 1931 (Box 3, Folder 117)
- Tunnell, John Welch 1942 (Box 3, Folder 118)
- Tyler, Mahlon James (Box 3, Folder 119)
- Utz, Donald Arthur 1938 (Box 3, Folder 120)
- Van Hise, Malcolm John 1943 (Box 3, Folder 121)
- Van Nest, Irvin D. 1940 (Box 3, Folder 122)
- Van Tassel, Lawrence Wilburn 1940 (Box 3, Folder 123)
- Van Vleet, George Jr. Grad (Box 3, Folder 124)
- Victor, Robert James 1943 (Box 3, Folder 125)
- Vitale, Paul Mario 1946 (Box 3, Folder 126)
- Voelker, Joseph Michael 1940 (Box 3, Folder 127)
- Vosper, Stephen Arnold 1942 (Box 3, Folder 128)
- Waldron, Arthur Slensby 1937 (Box 3, Folder 129)
- Wallace, John Martin 1934 (Box 3, Folder 130)
- Wallace, Robert James 1930 (Box 3, Folder 131)
- Walsh, Philip Sims 1939 (Box 3, Folder 132)
- Walton, Philip Coates Grad (Box 3, Folder 133)
- Wanrig, Richard James 1939 (Box 3, Folder 134)
- Way, Moncure Barton 1943 (Box 3, Folder 135)
- Ward, Brewster 1938 (Box 3, Folder 136)
- Weakland, William James Jr. 1936 (Box 3, Folder 137)
- Weiss, Lester 1941 (Box 3, Folder 138)
- Weaver, Thomas Cumpson 1945 (Box 3, Folder 139)
- Weissman, Bernard 1942 (Box 3, Folder 140)
- Wesley, John Harris 1942 (Box 3, Folder 141)
- Welch, Ross Warren 1947 (Box 3, Folder 142)